Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Motion Pictures Documenting Field Hockey
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, motion pictures documenting field hockey
1988-2003
RU 987
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
30.75
(123 videotapes)
The materials consist of videotapes created by the Department of Athletics documenting women's field hockey at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from the Department of Athletics, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of videotapes created by the Department of Athletics documenting women's field hockey at Yale.
College athletes; College sports; Field hockey; Motion pictures (visual works); Videotapes; Yale University -- Field hockey; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Women's field hockey game videotapes, 1988-2003; Accession 2006-A-062
  - "Clam diggers", 1988; videotape (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Yale, 1989; videotape (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Fairfield, 1990; videotape (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Highlight Tape, 1990; videotape (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Princeton, 1991 October 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 5)
  - UConn, 1991; videotape (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Highlight Tape, 1991; videotape (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Brown, 1992; videotape (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Harvard, 1992; videotape (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Princeton, 1992; videotape (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Springfield, 1992; videotape (VHS) (Box 11)
  - UConn, 1992; videotape (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Alumni Game, 1992; videotape (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Brown, 1993; videotape (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Dartmouth, 1993; videotape (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Harvard, 1993; videotape (VHS) (Box 16)
  - LaSalle, 1993; videotape (VHS) (Box 17)
  - UMass, 1993; videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Springfield, 1994 October 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Dartmouth, 1994 October 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Princeton, 1994 October 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Fairfield, 1994; videotape (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Holy Cross, 1994; videotape (VHS) (Box 23)
  - UConn, 1994; videotape (VHS) (Box 24)
  - UNH, 1995 August 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Ursinus, 1995 September 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Lehigh, 1995 September 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 27)
  - LaSalle, 1995 September 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 28)
  - Brown, 1995 September 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 29)
  - Harvard, 1995 October 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 30)
  - Cornell, 1995 October 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 31)
  - Princeton, 1995 October 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 32)
  - UPenn, 1995 October 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 33)
  - Fairfield, 1995; videotape (VHS) (Box 34)
  - Hofstra, 1995; videotape (VHS) (Box 35)
  - UMass, 1995; videotape (VHS) (Box 36)
  - Yale Skill Tape, 1995; videotape (VHS) (Box 37)
  - B.C., 1996 September 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 38)
  - Richmond, 1996 September 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 39)
  - William and Mary, 1996 September 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 39)
  - Rider, 1996 October 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 40)
  - Princeton, 1996 October 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 41)
  - Maine, 1996 October 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 42)
  - Columbia, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 43)
  - Cornell, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 44)
  - Hofstra, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 45)
  - Holy Cross, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 46)
  - Lehigh, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 47)
  - Maine, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 48)
  - UMass, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 49)
  - UPenn, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 50)
  - URI, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 51)
  - URI, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 52)
  - William and Mary, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 53)
  - Highlight Tape, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 54)
  - Preseason, 1997; videotape (VHS) (Box 55)
  - UNH, 1997 September 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 56)
  - Maine, 1997 September 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 57)
  - UMass, 1997 September 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 58)
  - Brown, 1997 September 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 59)
  - Fairfield, 1997 September 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 60)
  - Harvard, 1997 September 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 61)
  - Lehigh, 1997 October 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 62)
  - Providence, 1997 October 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 63)
  - Stanford, 1997 October 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 64)
  - Dartmouth, 1997 October 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 65)
  - Holy Cross, 1997 October 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 66)
  - Columbia, 1997 October 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 67)
  - Hofstra, 1997 October 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 68)
  - UPenn, 1997 November 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 69)
  - Cornell, 1997 November 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 70)
  - Season Highlights, 1997; videotape (VHS) (Box 71)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 71U)
  - Yale Field Hockey, 1998; videotape (VHS) (Box 73)
  - Season Highlights, 1998; videotape (VHS) (Box 74)
  - Greenwich Club Team, 2002 September 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 75)
  - Princeton, 2002 September 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 76)
  - Holy Cross, 2002 September 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 77)
  - Harvard, 2002 September 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 78)
  - Vermont, 2002 September 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 79)
  - New Hampshire, 2002 September 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 80)
  - Cornell, 2002 September 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 81)
  - UConn, 2002 October 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 82)
  - Boston University, 2002 October 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 83)
  - Quinnipiac, 2002 October 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 84)
  - Dartmouth, 2002 October 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 85)
  - Dartmouth, 2002 October 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 86)
  - University of the Pacific, 2002 October 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 87)
  - Stanford, 2002 October 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 88)
  - UPenn, 2002 October 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 89)
  - Sacred Heart, 2002 October 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 90)
  - Columbia, 2002 November 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 91)
  - Fairfield, 2002 November 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 92)
  - Brown, 2002 November 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 93)
  - Dartmouth, 2002 November 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 94)
  - Drexel, 2002 November 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 95)
  - Spring Tournament, 2002; videotape (VHS) (Box 96)
  - Spring Tournament, 2002; videotape (VHS) (Box 97)
  - Highlight Film, 2002; videotape (VHS) (Box 98)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 98U)
  - Yale Tournament, 2003 April 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 100)
  - Springfield Tournament, 2003 April 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 101)
  - Sacred Heart, 2003 September 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 102)
  - URI, 2003 September 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 103)
  - UNH, 2003 September 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 104)
  - BU, 2003 September 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 105)
  - Cornell, 2003 September 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 106)
  - Vermont, 2003 September 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 107)
  - UConn, 2003 October 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 108)
  - Quinnipiac, 2003 October 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 109)
  - Bucknell, 2003 October 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 110)
  - Harvard, 2003 October 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 111)
  - Holy Cross, 2003 October 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 112)
  - Penn, 2003 October 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 113)
  - Columbia, 2003 October 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 114)
  - Fairfield, 2003 November 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 115)
  - Penn, 2003 November 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 116)
  - Cornell, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 117)
  - Fairfield, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 118)
  - Greenwich Club, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 119)
  - Penn, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 120)
  - Princeton, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 121)
  - Springfield, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 122)
  - UNH, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 123)